Why are you wearing shorts? Are you kidding me?
No, no, no.
Maybe he's hiding.
Do you have a shot?
Let's go with that.
Director shorts.
Cue the director.
Director Shorts.
Live feed.
Go ahead.
Oh...
Oh, I see, I'm Subie's key.
Subie!
Hey, Subie!
Yes!
Oh, wow!
A woman coming out of the stone. It's not so easy, though.
It's coming out!
No, I mean, I don't know... I mean, you know...
I feel like talking about the climate.
Yes...
It's the rainy season right now.
It's not official yet, right?
That's right. So, the rainy season has begun.
Even if the weather bureau says it's the rainy season, it doesn't rain unexpectedly.
Oh, well, it does happen, doesn't it?
Yes, it does.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's hard to say, but it's humid.
But aren't there a lot of guerrilla rubber lately?
Yes, a lot.
It's like thunder forever.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
And it's really, you know, instantaneous.
It's like a pond.
It's amazing, isn't it?
But I'm surprised...everyone hates the rainy season, don't they?
That's right. Yes, that's right.
I think that during this period of the year, from the rainy season to the summer, it rains like crazy.
During this period, it rains like a flash.
I love this moment.
What do you like about it?
It's exciting.
Exciting?
What do you mean?
It's like the seasons are changing. It's raining hard.
Oh, I'm wet. I'm wet. It's starting to rain.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm a little embarrassed.
I'm sorry, I get embarrassed like that.
I'm embarrassed like that.
Even Nezumi gets wet in the rain.
Well, well, well... you know, I like the rain... but my hair's a little kinky, so it's really wavy.
I also get a lot of wavy hair... but it's nice to see frogs and toads on the side of the road.
Oh, there's that big one with the cows? They're coming out now.
They come out, and they sound like they're turning over.
It's got a high Saigel level.
I can't do it, can I?
Rainy season's a bit depressing, isn't it?
I see. Well, it's nice weather, isn't it? Moisture...
Well, even if I win, it won't mean anything.
If you think about it, you're right. What's your name?
If we talk about spring, summer, fall and winter, I like winter.
But when it's cold, you can put on more clothes.
You can't take it off. You're completely naked.
That's why it's hard. And there's snow and winter.
There are many events in winter, like Christmas, New Year's and Valentine's Day.
It's nice, isn't it? There are many romantic events in winter.
Yes, but also in the summer. We all go to the beach.
Yes, at the beach.
Like a beach house. A beach house, right?
You scared me. No, no, that's not what I meant.
I love beach houses.
I love the ocean.
No, no, no, no. I understand.
Well, well, well. If I had to choose, I'd say I love it, too.Well, well, well. If I had to choose whether I like it or not, I'd say I definitely like it.
I miss beach houses.
I miss eating at the beach house.
Fried noodles, fried rice... delicious, delicious, delicious, delicious.
Why did you choose it? It's delicious. What is it?
What is it that makes it so delicious?
I don't know who makes them these days, but they're pretty decent, aren't they?
I really want to go to a beach house.
I've heard there's a lot of beaches in Kanagawa, too.
Let's start with a quote.
I heard that there are many beaches in Kanagawa Prefecture, so I'll start with a quote.
I've never seen him before, so I thought he was a fat guy
I've never seen him before, so he's like a fat guy.
I'm like this, but I'm Johnny and I'm Pooze.
As you know, he is one of the biggest movie stars in the world.
Speaking of his masterpieces...
Pirates of the Caribbean.
Way, way, way, way, way...
Say it one more time.
Pirates of the Caribbean.
Watch out, I thought we were going to get meat.
Kabuli, like Calubian.
Calvillian, something like that.
Kabuli, Caribbean, Caribbean.
Like Caribbean, and all sorts of other things, like Charlie and the Chocolate Factory.
Yes, that's right.
Johnny Debbie just said it.
Maybe we should have Sarpong read it to you.
You sure?
It's kind of cool.
Yes, sir.
Okay, here we go. Johnny Depp said this.
Just a bad day, doesn't mean it's a bad life.
Cool. I guess it is when you say it with this dandy face.
I don't know why I'm saying that. I don't know, but...
I'm down, Johnny Depp.
I've had a great day, and I'm sure I'll wake up tomorrow with a different outlook on life, even if it's the last thing I did.Even if the last thing happens today, it will be different tomorrow.
I think Mr. Depp is saying that.
Mr. Depp doesn't say much.
From Johnny
Mr. Johnny
Johnny Depp.
He said...
Well... it's really casual.
But I really think...
Like this...
You shouldn't say things like this.
That's right.
You know, cool stuff like this...
We're the ones who have to say it.
It depends on how many times it comes out.
I mean...
What's the one thing I can beat Depp at? Loud.
I don't know. Johnny Depp could be really loud.
It could be great. You can't beat anything.
I'll do it. Master has a lot of charm.
Yes, he is.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, it's true. There are a lot of things.
You're not the neighbor's wife. Be confident.
You're still young.
Stop that kind of thing.
And... someone sent me a nice picture.
Let's see...
This one's of the insect variety.
You don't like them?
But it's not that kind.
Not that kind of insect.
It's like...
Really? It's like, wow. I'm looking forward to it. It's like, wow. Really? I believe you. Really? It's like, wow. I'm looking forward to it. It's like, wow. Really? I believe you.
Mr. Beale sent me. Thank you.
Good evening.
The rice paddies are flooded. I saw a very beautiful slender dragonfly for the first time.
Kingfisher Blue. I wish they were all this beautiful.
So there's a very beautiful dragonfly.
Oh, this one's a real beauty.
There's a dragonfly like this... like a highlighter.
Yes, it's amazing!
What a beautiful color!
A dragonfly like this exists... kingfisher blue, indeed.
I'm a dragonfly myself...
Ito dragonflies are sometimes found only in lakes...
It's very rare... in the rice paddies...
You don't see them around here.
It's so beautiful, it's like it's glowing.
I was sure you would say that, I was sure you would say that.
I thought you were going to say that right now.
It's beautiful. It's so cute! It's okay if it's like this.
And with this dragonfly... well, it's not an insect, but...
I'd like to introduce something cool.
I'd like to introduce something cool... from Ako, Hyogo Prefecture.
Thank you, Gazelle... for the Ako Ronin. I'm sure I mentioned something about them before.
You know “Chushingura,” right? What was it?
Oh, forget it... the Chushingura...
Chushingura is a period drama... that Sumie has never seen.
“Chushingura”...
The main character of “Chushingura” is a man from Ako.
Master Sarpon, my little Ebitui-chan. Good evening, Belle.
This is Uncle Ganhara, a.k.a. Master.
I heard that Raiya built a Gunpla under Master's influence, and I wanted to make one for the first time in a while, so I pulled it out of the closet and made one.
So I pulled the plastic model out of the closet and made it.
This is the Double-O, or is it the combined Double-O?
What's Double-O? It's like a “something riser”...
It combines?
Yeah. It's like a combined unit with better drive.
Wow!
Wow! Cool! Wow! Cool!
That's awesome! But you know, when you combine them...
It's so cool!
This is going to take a lot of time, isn't it?
No, I put decals and stuff on it.
Yes, yes, yes!
So many parts!
I'm working on it right now too!
New Gunpla!
Are you saying that now?
Oh, I'm telling you now?
I'll keep it a secret.
I don't need to keep it a secret.
Let's just keep it under wraps.
What year would you say it is?
But it's a recent one.
Recent.
There was finally a re-release of this one.
I got it.
Hohohohoho
Gunpla called
Hohoho
I'm looking forward to it!
It's totally like that, isn't it?
It's a Gunpla, isn't it?
I'm a little bit into it.
I looked at all kinds of things.
I was looking at all kinds of things, and I was wondering if there were tweezers or nail polish, so I went that way.
I bought a pen to put ink in the sea.
I heard it doesn't look very realistic!
I don't do anything, it'll just look like this.
But...
If you put a little bit of black stain here, it looks more realistic.
I'm sure she probably put some of it in.
I'm sure you're right.
I see... but it's been so long, I've forgotten about it.
Gundam models are short for Gundam plastic models.
What's that? Is it possible that someone in your family used to make them? Gunpla? What's that? Is it possible that someone in your family has been making them? Gunpla or something?
No? My brother made a lot of things with Legos. Legos are fashionable.
Lego is for girls... and I made this.
I was made to show them 100 Lego pieces...
I'm not saying it's not good... but it's not great for girls... it's a little bit different... but it's cool...
Anyway, the variety is great, but not so good...
The reason why there are plastic models in the first place is because there are so many original works.
There are a lot of original works... such as the Gundam Gundam... and the colors of the Gundam Gundam... are amazing.
There are many plastic models one after another, so the quality is very high.
And then there are enemy-type mobile suits.
And there are also enemy mobile suits, you know, like this one... yes, it's terrifying, isn't it?
I wonder if there is anyone in Japan who has made all of these.
I wonder how many shelves are needed to fill the room.
I'm going to need a lot of shelves for the first one alone...
Just thinking about it...
Well, well, well, well...
And... Mr. Serpon took a picture of me.
Which one shall we start with? The top one.
Just the other day... in Yokosuka... at the Yokosuka Art Museum...
Toshio Suzuki and Ghibli exhibition.
I was able to go, and it was really amazing.
I wonder what kind of games he used to play as a child, or how he used to play “hate catch-ball”... I got to know such detailed information about him, you know, wall-to-wall guessing.
So it was a lot of fun.
You know, a guest came to the party, right?
You know, the guest said that he had collected books one by one.
And he also said he collected DVDs.
There was a tremendous amount of them.
Wow!
Really.
That's why you love movies so much.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, you get a lot of ideas from books.
I could see how great you are.
I could see how great you are. I visited your place, right?
Mr. Wataridan's office, well, it's a lot of different rooms for different purposes, but...
The room where I interviewed him was filled with DVDs of movies and stuff like that.
I'm sure there were books and stuff in there too.
It's not good, is it? It's bad, isn't it?
So there are famous works, and then there are works that I don't know.
I'm not sure if I'm familiar with some of them, but there are recent works from all eras.
And not only that, there's a lot more.
Uberber, this is a fortune.
There's a string in the mouth, and you pull it out, and the number that comes out is written on the shelf, and you go to the shelf and take it.
The second one, the third one, the third one...
What happens? Uberber is a love fortune.
And this is a love fortune, and it came out “Chukichi”...
And Zenibar...
Zenibar is a place where you can not only look at the fortune, but also enjoy it.
It was a lot of fun.
This is the shelf, right?
The kamaji? Yes, yes.
It was filled with medicinal herbs.
That sounds like fun. It was a lot of fun.
You know...
I think it's still open.
But a medium fortune is the most boring.
Please stop it, I got a “Chukichi” fortune.
I think it's halfway.
I'll do “Chukichi” too. I'm thinking of changing my name to “Chukichi”.
That's how much you'll get?
Yes! I can't remember ever getting anything other than “Chukichi”.
Really?
I don't even have a “big” luck.
So what's that? Big luck, good luck, medium luck, small luck...
Like today... In order...
I'd say you're right in the middle.
It's harmless.
You can have a bland love life.
Really? Really?
It's bland.
Well, that's good.
If nothing else.
If there's nothing else, I'm sure there were a lot of nostalgic things from the Master's generation.
I think there was a lot of nostalgia. It's like the Showa Era.
Animage magazine... I think it was a magazine called Animage or something like that.
That's what you were working on, wasn't it?
Yes, that's right. Like an editor.
That's how you met, right? At Mr. Miyazaki's place.
Very often.
But he wrote some great quotes.
Mr. Suzuki, I can say the same thing.
That's right. And calligraphy, too.
I can do both calligraphy and art.
I can do both calligraphy and art, so I only need to get serious once every three months.
There was a quote like that.
You were wearing a nightgown during the interview. Well, I wasn't really serious.
It wasn't exactly the day of the once-every-three-months interview, but he was really trying to make the job fun and easy.
It did look fun and easy, because it was like a sweatshirt.
So that's where it all came out. I really learned a lot about life.
Oh, that's it. It says “Kesera-sera” on it.
Kesera-sera. That's right.
It's a line from the famous scene of Ghibli...
It was really fun!
I'm sure you'll have a great time!
Yes, it's in Yokosuka. Please go. You went to Yokosuka?
Yes, I did. I drove there.
We're driving. He's so cool! He's so mature!
You're a grown-up! You should go there in a hurry. Yokosuka's got great roads.
There's also the ocean. I think the museum goes that way to the ocean.
That's right. On the way, there's a road with tropical trees.
We were driving along the road with music blasting.
What kind of music did you play?
There's a band called Penthouse. I love them.
I love their music.
There's a band.
It's cool.
I think you're lying.
Why are you so obvious?
Half of it's not true.
It's true.
Maybe the car is real, but I think your dad's driving it.
Not at all. I went alone. No, I went alone.
I went to the store alone.
Ew.
I had the sashimi set and left.
How can you eat alone?
Alone most of the time.
You don't have to say it.
My image of you is that you're usually at your dad's.
Yes, that's right.
My dad was working.
I had no choice.
If he was off, I'd go with him.
Well, well, well... that's why I'm here.
Please visit Yokosuka, everyone!
Yes, yes
So...
This week, it's SUBIE
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Subie is kind of shining... shining... shining... shining... shining...
She's shining... I feel like she's running...
He's running like this... he's Debel Charging Subie's allowance because she's so cute...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
It's here! Want to buy some? Are you good at that kind of stuff?
I like them a lot... like those 2,000-piece puzzles.
I used to do that when I was little. I'm sure you'll be more interested in Subie than in Gunpla.
I don't need any glue to make them nowadays.
I want to try it!
The quality is too high for my sisters.
Fingers move like this.
I see.
Move them.
Everything is separate.
It's amazing!
When you put it on, it moves like this.
That's great!
I'm going to buy it.
By all means, by all means.
Okay, that Devil's Charge. Then that Devil Charge.
No, you can't use Devil's Charge.
You're going to dress it up.
But we're here for Subie...
I mean... what's usually in the regenerator...
You can't do that.
The logo of rebirth.
Good luck on your spring tour!
I'll do my best.
July is the month, right?
July 27th and 28th are in Osaka.
This week is Aichi. I will be in Aichi on Saturday.
I'm looking forward to Aichi, too.
But you are too busy to explore the city.
That's right. I can only get a sense of the local area from the food that is brought in.
In Nagoya, do they bring in things like chicken wings?
In Nagoya, last year or the year before, they served hitsu-mabushi for dinner and hitsu-mabushi for bento.
It was so delicious that it came with hot water and was ready at the end of the meal, and you could eat all sorts of things with it.
Hitsumabushi catering is amazing.
It's amazing.
What the heck.
It's amazing. Momoshiki-san, thank you for making me a gasoline expert too. It's a big help. Gasoline is still expensive these days.
It is expensive, isn't it? It is expensive.
Thank you very much. Yes, yes, yes. Well, well, well.
Well, see you next week at 8:00, 8:00 p.m. Let's all meet again at 8:00.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's go!
Charachter.
Okay, bye, bye!
This one, this one's good.
Ha!
Ah!